<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Santiago Forero</title>
        <link>https://forero.ga/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Santiago Forero</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 18:15:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://forero.ga/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Day 3</title>
            <link>https://forero.ga/posts/day-3/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 18:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://forero.ga/posts/day-3/</guid>
            <description>Day: 3 Date: Wednesday, August 26, 2021  This was just a normal day, I spent my day in online classes and homework.
I was going to have training but it was canceled because Bogotá had had public order problems. Instead I was supposed to do my own training, but I was really lazy so I decided to do something very very calm.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><strong>Day:</strong> 3</li>
<li><strong>Date:</strong> Wednesday, August 26, 2021</li>
</ul>
<p>This was just a normal day, I spent my day in online classes and homework.</p>
<p>I was going to have training but it was canceled because Bogotá had had public order problems. Instead I was supposed to do my own training, but I was really lazy so I decided to do something very very calm.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>A New Day</title>
            <link>https://forero.ga/posts/a-new-day/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 19:28:21 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://forero.ga/posts/a-new-day/</guid>
            <description>Day: 2 Date: Wednesday, August 25, 2021  Today was a just a normal day, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have classes, although I used my free time to do some homework from school, I even redacted an essay about death penalty, I didn&amp;rsquo;t enjoy doing it.
Me and my family were thinking about getting me vaccinated but we finally decided that I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t do it yet, because I&amp;rsquo;m having an athletics competition really soon and I want to avoid side effects.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><strong>Day:</strong> 2</li>
<li><strong>Date:</strong> Wednesday, August 25, 2021</li>
</ul>
<p>Today was a just a normal day, I didn&rsquo;t have classes, although I used my free time to do some homework from school, I even redacted an essay about death penalty, I didn&rsquo;t enjoy doing it.</p>
<p>Me and my family were thinking about getting me vaccinated but we finally decided that I shouldn&rsquo;t do it yet, because I&rsquo;m having an athletics competition really soon and I want to avoid side effects.</p>
<p>I also spent some time on my pc, I created a new linux user and started creating my dotfiles, they are available <a href="https://github.com/forerosantiago/dotfiles">here</a> by the way.</p>
<p>In the afternoon I went with my sister to walk around the neighborhood, and finally at 7PM played in a chess tournament, I didn&rsquo;t do very well because I was tired.</p>
<p>Today I want to talk about my chess career today, so I started playing a lot of chess online during the pandemic, I really enjoy it and have improved by a lot, everything I learned a lot of stuff online, which made me a player who is better than the average person, I still consider myself a beginner though&hellip;</p>
<p>Recently like a week ago, I met a friend online who studies in the National University, he told me about a chess club, and I joined, which made me really happy. It was a little bit hard for me to be able to join since this program is for uni students, and I&rsquo;m not there yet, however I told the teacher about my school (which belongs to the National University) and he let me in. I think this is a really nice opportunity to improve and meet new people.</p>
<p>At the moment of writing this I am really tired, so I apologize if there are any mistakes in this post. Thank you and have a nice day.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Day 1</title>
            <link>https://forero.ga/posts/day-1/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 20:41:33 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://forero.ga/posts/day-1/</guid>
            <description>Day: 1 Date: Tuesday, August 25, 2021  Dear readers, Today is the first day of my e-diary, a project that aims to document my life and share thoughts and ideas.
I woke up at around 6:40 in the morning, took a shower, brushed my teeth and started my virtual school day, I do not enjoy virtual classes anymore, I&amp;rsquo;m tired of them, I believe that 1.5+ years of virtual school is enough for me, I cannot wait to go to the irl school.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><strong>Day:</strong> 1</li>
<li><strong>Date:</strong> Tuesday, August 25, 2021</li>
</ul>
<p>Dear readers,
Today is the first day of my e-diary, a project that aims to document my life and share thoughts and ideas.</p>
<p>I woke up at around 6:40 in the morning, took a shower, brushed my teeth and started my virtual school day, I do not enjoy virtual classes anymore, I&rsquo;m tired of them, I believe that 1.5+ years of virtual school is enough for me, I cannot wait to go to the irl school.</p>
<p>Until around 12PM my classes finally ended, I had my lunch and went to my athletics training (I&rsquo;m getting started in the athletics world, and I&rsquo;m already having a competition the saturday) from 3PM to 5PM, I believe it was the best part of my day.</p>
<p>I really enjoy doing athleticism and I think it&rsquo;s a really nice way to spend my time. Today was my second day training with <strong>IDRD</strong> (Instituto Distrital de Recreación y Deporte) for free! Isn&rsquo;t it amazing? Today I worked on my running speed and practiced bit of javelin throwing, it isn&rsquo;t as hard as I thought it would be, but it still requires technique and concentration.</p>
<p>This is a little summary of my day, it was a normal day, nothing special, I did enjoy a lot today&rsquo;s training.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>My new website</title>
            <link>https://forero.ga/posts/my-new-website/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:16:02 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://forero.ga/posts/my-new-website/</guid>
            <description>Hello there, I&amp;rsquo;m glad you found my website, my small corner of the internet, you may be wondering what is this place, right? Well, this is my blog, yep, this is just another blog in the world wide web.
I have had several failed attempts of a personal website/blog, they all looked terrible, I tried using php layouts, jekyll, plain HTML, etc&amp;hellip; but the results weren&amp;rsquo;t really nice for me :( (probably because I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to use them appropriately), so I decided to give premade themes a try with hugo, so far so good, it&amp;rsquo;s been working perfectly fine and it&amp;rsquo;s certainly better than my themes, the theme the website uses right now is called hello-friend-ng.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello there, I&rsquo;m glad you found my website, my small corner of the internet, you may be wondering what is this place, right? Well, this is my blog, yep, this is just another blog in the world wide web.</p>
<p>I have had several failed attempts of a personal website/blog, they all looked terrible, I tried using php layouts, jekyll, plain HTML, etc&hellip; but the results weren&rsquo;t really nice for me :( (probably because I don&rsquo;t know how to use them appropriately), so I decided to give premade themes a try with  <a href="https://gohugo.io/">hugo</a>, so far so good, it&rsquo;s been working perfectly fine and it&rsquo;s certainly better than my themes, the theme the website uses right now is called <a href="https://themes.gohugo.io/themes/hugo-theme-hello-friend-ng/">hello-friend-ng</a>. It&rsquo;s pretty simple but I like it :D</p>
<h2 id="the-blog">The blog</h2>
<p>My blog is a place to express, give opinions and share thoughts and ideas.</p>
<p>This is the first post of my blog, I plan to write at least one short post everyday talking about my day, feelings, what I learned, etc. This kind of journal will be a fun way to document my life and practice my redaction skills. All these posts will have the <a href="http://forero.ga/tags/daily/">daily tag</a></p>
<p>Additionally there will be less frecuent long posts about a topic in specific.</p>
<h2 id="the-end">The end</h2>
<p>Thank you for reading my post, I hope you enjoyed and stay tunned!</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
